<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Todd Pipe &amp; Supply</title>
    <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Todd Pipe &amp; Supply</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Todd Pipe &amp; Supply, LLC. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 15:36:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://toddpipe.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Price Updates</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/resources/price-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 18:19:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/resources/price-updates/</guid>
      <description>  Effective Date Price Change &amp;#43;/- Manufacturer     07/02/2018 &amp;#43;12% Charlotte Pipe   07/02/2018 &amp;#43;12% Charlotte Pipe   07/02/2018 &amp;#43;12% Charlotte Pipe   07/02/2018 &amp;#43;12% Charlotte Pipe   07/02/2018 &amp;#43;12% Charlotte Pipe   07/02/2018 &amp;#43;12% Charlotte Pipe   07/02/2018 &amp;#43;12% Charlotte Pipe       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Info</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/resources/product-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 17:35:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/resources/product-information/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 16:41:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email us  info@toddpipe.com   Call Us  (714) 688-2560    Employment  Visit Career Center     Send Us a Message First Name *  Last Name *   Company Name *  Email *  Phone    Nearest Branch * Select... Anaheim Hawthorne Riverside San Diego Sylmar West LA   I am a... * Select... Licensed Plumber General Contractor Homeowner Other   How did you hear about us?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturers</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/manufacturers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 15:36:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/manufacturers/</guid>
      <description>Bathware / Shower   Bootz Fiat Florestone  Cast Iron Pipe / Fittings   Charlotte Pipe  Cast Iron Sinks  Commercial Enamaling  Chinaware  American Standard Gerber Mansfield Toto Vortens Western Pottery  Drains  Ebbe (Ebbe America) Frank Pattern Jay R. Smith Josam Mifab Silverwind Wade (Mega Western Sales) Watts (Delco Sales) Zurn  Faucets  American Standard Chicago Faucets Clevland Danze Delta Faucets Fisher Grohe Krowne (Carrhill) Matco Moen Olympia Peerless Pioneer Price Pfister Sloan Symmons T &amp;amp; S Brass Toto Zurn  Fittings / Connections  Anvil Brasscraft Copper Fittings Dahl Dearborn Brass Fluid Master Husky / Anaco Couplings Ideal NH Couplings (Mainline Sales) LSP (LSP Specialty Products) Matco NH Couplings (Mainline Sales) Mission Rubber Nibco Omega Flex PVC / DWV Fittings PVC Pipe PVC Pressure Fittings SDR 35 Fittings Sharkbite EvoPex (Mega Western Sales) Sioux Chief Uponor Viega Press &amp;amp; Crimp Pex Viega Raidant  Flashing / Venting  Duravent Hart &amp;amp; Cooley  Flush Valves  American Standard AMTC Sloan Toto Zurn  Garbage Disposals ISE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Not Sell My Information</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/do-not-sell-my-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 13:58:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/do-not-sell-my-information/</guid>
      <description>Under the California Consumer Privacy Act, California residents may have the right to opt-out of data collection, to request a copy of their personal information, or to request deletion of their personal information. To make a request, please fill out the form below or email your request to privacy@toddpipe.com First Name *  Last Name *   Email *  Phone    Request- Type * Opt-out of data collection Export personal data Delete personal data    Message   Submit Request  Fields marked * are required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebates</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/resources/rebates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 13:43:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/resources/rebates/</guid>
      <description>SoCal Water$mart Premium High-Efficiency Toilets  View  Energy Star ENERGY STAR Rebate Finder  View      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Employees</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/about/our-employees/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 13:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/about/our-employees/</guid>
      <description>Kim Tran Controller Did you know Kim sponsors the Choc Walk in the Park every year? To show your support or donate to Kim’s team, e-mail Kim. E-mail Kim        Jimmy Martin Warehouse Manager Did you know Jim is a certified Divemaster? Click the link to check out some of his photo’s. View Gallery        James David Aguirre Driver Did you know that James David Aguirre is an author?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Careers</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/careers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 13:33:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/careers/</guid>
      <description>Email us  hr@toddpipe.com   Call Us  (866) 345-5552    Fax Us  (909) 494-4075      Todd Pipe is always looking for qualified candiates to fill positions. Download Application </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sylmar</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/locations/sylmar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 08:42:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/locations/sylmar/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West LA</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/locations/west-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 08:41:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/locations/west-la/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forms</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/resources/forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 20:09:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/resources/forms/</guid>
      <description>COD Credit Card Authorization Authorization form for Cash On Delivery customers  Download  Credit Application This form is required to apply for a credit account  Download  Credit Card Authorization Authorization form for all non-COD customers  Download  Job Start For a job account to begin releasing material  Download  Joint Check Agreement For General Contractors paying for materials of Sub-Contrators  Download  Sales Tax Exemption Form required for your account to be tax-exempt  Download  Employment Application To join Todd Pipe&amp;#39;s team, fill out this application  Download      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Riverside</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/locations/riverside/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 19:25:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/locations/riverside/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/locations/san-diego/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 19:23:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/locations/san-diego/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/legal/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 15:01:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/legal/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply, LLC, a California corporation (with its affiliates, &amp;ldquo;Todd Pipe&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Todd&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;) owns and operates a website with a home page located at www.toddpipe.com (including linked/connected websites, collectively, the &amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo;). We value the privacy of individuals who visit the Site (the &amp;ldquo;User(s)&amp;quot;, or &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo;). This Website Privacy Policy (this &amp;ldquo;Privacy Policy&amp;rdquo;) has been created to inform Users of the types of individual and technical information that is or may be collected on the Site and the privacy policies and practices that Todd follows with respect to the use and dissemination of such information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>California Prop 65</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/prop65/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 14:55:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/prop65/</guid>
      <description>Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply is committed to complying with all applicable laws and regulations pertaining to the products we distribute. The California Safe Drinking Water and Toxic Enforcement Act of 1986, also known as Proposition 65, requires clear and reasonable warnings for products that can expose individuals to any one of the 900-plus chemicals on the Proposition 65 list. New Proposition 65 warning regulations became fully effective on August 30, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 14:47:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/terms/</guid>
      <description>1. Entire Agreement In the event that credit is extended by Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply, LLC to the applicant named on the attached Application for Credit (“Buyer”) or Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply, LLC otherwise sells any products to Buyer, the attached Application for Credit and these Terms and Conditions shall constitute anagreement (“Agreement”) between Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply, LLC and Buyer. Each sale by Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply, LLC or its affiliates (collectively “Seller”) to Buyer shall be subject to these Terms and Conditions, whichshall prevail over any inconsistent terms of Buyer&amp;rsquo;s purchase orders or other documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/posts/covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 14:28:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/posts/covid-19/</guid>
      <description>At MORSCO, the health and safety of our Customers, Team Members, and communities we live in and service is a top priority. As many of you have heard, the Coronavirus (COVID-19) is having an increased impact around the world. It is important that we remain pragmatic and sensible about how we can keep one another safe. MORSCO takes this responsibility seriously and asks that each of us, individually, do the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 13:49:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply would like to personally thank our Contractors &amp;amp; Suppliers for your overwhelming support in opening Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply. Here at Todd Pipe, we strive for customer satisfaction in every aspect of our business. Providing our Contractors with the industry’s most knowledgeable sales staff and competitively priced material, when and where it’s needed, is our absolute #1 goal. We know of the many choices available to our customers and simply put… its our job to make the decision of where you buy an easy one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawthorne</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/locations/hawthorne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 10:07:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/locations/hawthorne/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anaheim</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/locations/anaheim/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 19:34:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/locations/anaheim/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>