<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Legal on Todd Pipe &amp; Supply</title>
    <link>https://toddpipe.netlify.app/company/legal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Legal on Todd Pipe &amp; Supply</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Todd Pipe &amp; Supply, LLC. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 13:32:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://toddpipe.netlify.app/company/legal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Not Sell My Information</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.netlify.app/do-not-sell-my-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 13:58:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.netlify.app/do-not-sell-my-information/</guid>
      <description>Under the California Consumer Privacy Act, California residents may have the right to opt-out of data collection, to request a copy of their personal information, or to request deletion of their personal information. To make a request, please fill out the form below or email your request to privacy@toddpipe.com First Name *  Last Name *   Email *  Phone    Request- Type * Opt-out of data collection Export personal data Delete personal data    Message   Submit Request  Fields marked * are required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.netlify.app/company/legal/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 15:01:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.netlify.app/company/legal/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply, LLC, a California corporation (with its affiliates, &amp;ldquo;Todd Pipe&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Todd&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;) owns and operates a website with a home page located at www.toddpipe.com (including linked/connected websites, collectively, the &amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo;). We value the privacy of individuals who visit the Site (the &amp;ldquo;User(s)&amp;quot;, or &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo;). This Website Privacy Policy (this &amp;ldquo;Privacy Policy&amp;rdquo;) has been created to inform Users of the types of individual and technical information that is or may be collected on the Site and the privacy policies and practices that Todd follows with respect to the use and dissemination of such information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>California Prop 65</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.netlify.app/prop65/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 14:55:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.netlify.app/prop65/</guid>
      <description>Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply is committed to complying with all applicable laws and regulations pertaining to the products we distribute. The California Safe Drinking Water and Toxic Enforcement Act of 1986, also known as Proposition 65, requires clear and reasonable warnings for products that can expose individuals to any one of the 900-plus chemicals on the Proposition 65 list. New Proposition 65 warning regulations became fully effective on August 30, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.netlify.app/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 14:47:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.netlify.app/terms/</guid>
      <description>1. Entire Agreement In the event that credit is extended by Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply, LLC to the applicant named on the attached Application for Credit (“Buyer”) or Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply, LLC otherwise sells any products to Buyer, the attached Application for Credit and these Terms and Conditions shall constitute anagreement (“Agreement”) between Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply, LLC and Buyer. Each sale by Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply, LLC or its affiliates (collectively “Seller”) to Buyer shall be subject to these Terms and Conditions, whichshall prevail over any inconsistent terms of Buyer&amp;rsquo;s purchase orders or other documents.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>