<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Company on Todd Pipe &amp; Supply</title>
    <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Company on Todd Pipe &amp; Supply</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Todd Pipe &amp; Supply, LLC. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 15:34:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://toddpipe.github.io/company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 16:41:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email us  info@toddpipe.com   Call Us  (714) 688-2560    Employment  Visit Career Center     Send Us a Message First Name  Last Name   Company Name  Email   Phone    Nearest Branch Select... Anaheim Hawthorne Riverside San Diego Sylmar West LA   I am a... Select... Licensed Plumber General Contractor Homeowner Other   How did you hear about us?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Employees</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/employees/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 13:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/employees/</guid>
      <description>Kim Tran Controller Did you know Kim sponsors the Choc Walk in the Park every year? To show your support or donate to Kim’s team, e-mail Kim. E-mail Kim        Jimmy Martin Warehouse Manager Did you know Jim is a certified Divemaster? Click the link to check out some of his photo’s. View Gallery        James David Aguirre Driver Did you know that James David Aguirre is an author?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Careers</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/careers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 13:33:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/careers/</guid>
      <description>Email us  hr@toddpipe.com   Call Us  (866) 345-5552    Fax Us  (909) 494-4075      Todd Pipe is always looking for qualified candiates to fill positions. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 13:49:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toddpipe.github.io/company/about/</guid>
      <description>Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply would like to personally thank our Contractors &amp;amp; Suppliers for your overwhelming support in opening Todd Pipe &amp;amp; Supply. Here at Todd Pipe, we strive for customer satisfaction in every aspect of our business. Providing our Contractors with the industry’s most knowledgeable sales staff and competitively priced material, when and where it’s needed, is our absolute #1 goal. We know of the many choices available to our customers and simply put… its our job to make the decision of where you buy an easy one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>